[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "name": "Steven",
        "location": "Erfurt",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Will there still be smartphones around?"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "name": "Maria",
        "location": "Verona",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Will we still be using physical tools?"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "name": "Matthias",
        "location": "Weimar",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Will humans have technological implants? "
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "name": "Jasmin",
        "location": "Jena",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Will people still write with characters?"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "name": "Donna",
        "location": "Weimar",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "How will humans use algorithms for health purposes?"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "name": "",
        "location": "",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Will ai replace me?"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "name": "",
        "location": "",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "do we drift apart even more within the communiaction channels we have? "
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "name": "Deckard",
        "location": "Los Angeles",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Is it gonna be like in Blade Runner ? "
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "name": "Moch",
        "location": "Thailand",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "What can AI help shape the education in the future?"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "name": "Isa",
        "location": "Colombia",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Are we doomed?"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "name": "Yasmine",
        "location": "Tangier",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Will arts and crafts still be relevant in 100 years"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "name": "Chris",
        "location": "Earth",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "When will I not have to type stuff in keyboards on devices anymore?"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "name": "Lukas",
        "location": "Hamburg",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Who will profit from the work, which is taken over by AI and not done by humans anymore?"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "name": "Lukas",
        "location": "Hamburg",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Will AI teach us social interaction?"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "name": "Lea",
        "location": "CROATIA",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "When is teleporting becoming a reality?"
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "name": "Otto",
        "location": "Norway",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Should we exist?"
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "name": "Svenja ",
        "location": "Deutschland ",
        "question": "Question to the Future",
        "answer": "Was wird Bildung bedeuten?"
    }
]